# Radhika Wagh

Thane, IN | radhika.wagh85@gmail.com | +91 9869983605

# **Professional Summary**

Enthusiastic customer service professional with over 6+ years of experience in Service Industry. Highly motivated and outgoing individual with proven ability of addressing & resolving customer issues. Competent team player who can successfully inspire fellow colleagues.

#### **Key Areas of Impact**

- Excellent Communication Skills
- Problem solving
- Good Interpersonal Skills
- Team Leadership
- Attentiveness
- Fast Learner

- Time Management
- Resilience
- Conflict resolution

#### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

#### **Acko General Insurance**

#### **Worked as a Customer Care Executive**

Sept 2021 to Aug 2022

- Policy Status and Claim Update, Registering the Claim, Policy Endorsement, Handling Escalations.
- Development Strength & Improve Weaknesses.
- Inspire Team members by Setting an example.
- Listen to Team members feedback and take necessary actions.
- End to end resolution & quality customer service approach towards getting a suitable outcome.
- Escalating on emails wherever needed.

#### ACRO Solution (LWD- 15th Feb 2021).

#### **Worked as a Customer Care Executive**

Feb 2017 to Feb 2021

- To respond for customer fresh enquiries via phone and emails.
- To resolve the issues of existing customers and closing the complaints in TAT time.
- To coordinate with the suppliers for the rate of the company products.
- To prepare a market comparative analysis report for the rate of the industrial safety products.
- To coordinate for customer invoices and courier and ensure to keep the database of the customer invoices.

### **Tata Consultancy Services**

June 2012 to Dec 2012

#### Worked as a Sr. Process Associate Taj Inner Circle Process)

- To communicate with customers and provide the details of benefits for premium membership.
- To send timely information of membership offers to the customers via email.
- To raise complaints and ensure to close the open complaints within TAT.

#### Worked as a Sr. Customer Care Executive - International Air Ticketing (TQR)

- Handling Customer Service Calls from existing and new US customers.
- Follow ups with customers for new and existing reservations, name change or schedule change.
- To coordinate with airlines for schedule change or cancellation of bookings.
- To help customers for smooth refund process in case of cancellation.
- To raise the customer complaints in SABER software & to follow up with the airlines for the TAT closure.

#### **COMPUTER PROFICIENCY**

• MS -Office

#### **CREDENTIALS**

## Bachelors Certifications

Bachelor of Arts from University of Mumbai, 2008

- International Air Transport Associate Level 1 Foundation Course- International Air Fare Desk Form IITC Mumbai, 2008
- Diploma in Computer Application and Management Ramnarayan Ruia College, Mumbai, 2005
  Excellence in Public Speaking & Leadership (Indo American Society) Mumbai, 2008